ABOUT ME

Studying in a computer engineering school, I am interested in software development and engineering. I would like to get experience in the phases and methodologies of the development process. I am enthusiatic about technology products that deliver new solutions.

CONTACTS

E-mail: sami.benamar67@gmail.com **Linkedin**: https://www.linkedin.com

/in/sami-benamar/

Phone Number: +33 781 406 718

Website:

https://samibenamar.github.io/portfolio/

LANGUAGES

- French (Native)
- English

SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Project management
- Communication
- Adaptability
- PHP
- NodeJS
- MySQL
- HTML/CSS
- Javascript
- C++/C#
- Java
- Python
- Arduino
- Networking base

HOBBIES

- Tennis, ranked 32 practiced 3 years
- School trips to Dublin in 2014 and Budapest in 2018
- Programming, website creation for 5 years

SAMI BENAMAR

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

B&S Robsim

Apprenticeship 2021-2022

- Development of a mobile robot fleet management system in Python
- Creation of a 3d display to visualize the movement of robots in the factory in C++ with Unreal Engine
- Development of HMI in Python
- Development of a mobile application for industrial line monitoring with Flutter

B&S Robsim

Internship scheduled from April 6, 2021 to July 30, 2021

• Development of a Cobot robot capable of palletizing, handling and screwing. It is intended to help areas where the pace slows down.

B&S Robsim

Developer from August 3, 2020 to September 11, 2020

- Programming to automate a miniature robotic line in C.
- Development of a mobile application in Java with Android Studio to remotely control the robotic line.

Creation of programs and websites

2016 - 2020

- Creation of my web agency https://fadnex.fr
- Development of various websites. (PHP, HTML/CSS, Javascript, NodeJS)
- Development of a stock management and invoicing software for Alsace Media Center. (C++)

EDUCATION

CESI School of Engineering Strasbourg

Apprenticeship 2021-2024

- Engineering training in the field of computer science.
- Apprenticeship in the company B&S Robsim.

CESI School of Engineering Strasbourg

Integrated preparation 2019-2021

- Engineer training in the field of computer science.
- President of the Bureau Des Sports association.

High School Heinrich-Nessel

2016-2019

 Scientific baccalaureate, engineering science option, mathematics speciality, European section English. Mention Bien.